const questionsArray = [
    {
        "question": "What does HTML means?",
        "answers": [
            "Hot TaMaLe",
            "High Transition Markup Lines",
            "HyperText Markup Language",
            "HyperTransfer Metabyte Loader"
        ],
        "validAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of these tags does not exist?",
        "answers": [
            "<a>",
            "<article>",
            "<center>",
            "<span>"
        ],
        "validAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one is not an align-items valid value?",
        "answers": [
            "center",
            "baseline",
            "flex-start",
            "flex-middle"
        ],
        "validAnswer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Let's talk Javascript. What causes variable shadowing?",
        "answers": [
            "Assigning different values to the same variable in different scopes",
            "Assigning different names to variables with the same values",
            "Declaring a let variable in a function scope",
            "Declaring a const variable in a global scope"
        ],
        "validAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which styles of writing are considered best practices for CSS, Js functions and Js classes, respectively?",
        "answers": [
            "Snake case, Pascal case and Camel case",
            "Camel case for all",
            "Snake case, Camel Case and Pascal case",
            "Kebab case, Camel Case and Pascal case"
        ],
        "validAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you call map, filter and reduce?",
        "answers": [
            "Variable methods",
            "Array methods",
            "Array functions",
            "Function arrays"
        ],
        "validAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one does not have a syntax error?",
        "answers": [
            "array.reduce((a, b) => a + b)",
            "<a href='https://www.google.com'/>",
            "function multiply(a; b) { return a * b }",
            `const person = {
                name = 'Jane';
                lastName = 'Doe'
            }`
        ],
        "validAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What does HTML means?",
        "answers": [
            "Hot TaMaLe",
            "High Transition Markup Lines",
            "HyperText Markup Language",
            "HyperTransfer Metabyte Loader"
        ],
        "validAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What defines  ",
        "answers": [
            "Hot TaMaLe",
            "High Transition Markup Lines",
            "HyperText Markup Language",
            "HyperTransfer Metabyte Loader"
        ],
        "validAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What makes Javascript an asynchronous language?",
        "answers": [
            "It's async/await functions",
            "The fact that we can use promises",
            "The fact that it can execute commands in an orderly fashion",
            "Javascript is not an asynchronous language"
        ],
        "validAnswer": 4
    },
]